A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.27 (A2001) FA488
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2001.012: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2000; AC.2001.012; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
  - Bellagio Conference and Study Center, 120; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (KUPER, ADAM JONATHAN), 1995-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LAITIN, DAVID D.), 1995-1998 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LAKE, LOUIS-ALBERT) (CO-RESIDENT: TOURE, EL HADJ SEYDOU NOUROU) (DID NOT GO), 1996-1997 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LAM, BUN-CHING) (CO-RESIDENT: KALDEWEY, GUNNAR A.), 1994-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LANGER, JUDITH A.), 1993-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LAPOINTE, ARCHIE E.), 1994-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LARSON, EDWARD J.), 1995-1997 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LATIN, HOWARD A.), 1995-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LAYISH-SHEPHERD, NAOMI), 1993-1994 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LEE, HOCHOL), 1995-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LENNON, JOHN ANTHONY), 1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LEONEL, MAURO DE MELLO, Jr.), 1993-1995 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LESCH, ANN MOSELY), 1995-1999 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LEVIANT, CURT), 1995-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LEVIN, GAIL), 1992-1996 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LEVINE, LAWRENCE W.), 1994-1995 (Box R3392)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LEVINE, MICHAEL P.), 1992-1995 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LEVINE, PHILIP), 1993-1995 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LEWONTIN, RICHARD C.), 1992-1994 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LIEHM, ANTONIN J.), 1993-1995 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LIGON, GLENN), 1993-1996 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LINDENBERGER, HERBERT S.), 1995-1996 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LINNEY, ROMULUS), 1995-1996 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LI SHI-YE), 1993-1997 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LJUNGGREN, BORJE), 1993-1994 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LOGAN, WENDELL MORRIS), 1992-1994 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LONGINO, HELEN E.), 1993-1995 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LOPEZ-ORTEGA, ANTONIO), 1993-1996 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LORD, CATHERINE), 1995-1996 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LUNENFELD, MARVIN), 1993-1994 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (LUO XIANHUA) (CO-RESIDENT: WEI SUXIAN), 1993-1995 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MCFEELY, MARY DRAKE), 1992-2000 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MCFEELY, WILLIAM S.), 1992-1995 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MCKAY, SUSAN ANN R.), 1995-1997 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MACK, CAROL R.), 1993-1997 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MAHMOUD, ADEL A. F.), 1996-1997 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MANACHINO DE PEREZ ROLDAN, ISABEL), 1994-1996 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MANN, BRUCE H.), 1994-1997 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MAOZ, ZEEV), 1995-1996 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MARCHESCHI, DANIELA), 1995-1996 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MARK, JOAN TEPASKE), 1996 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MARRANCA, BONNIE), 1993-1995 (Box R3393)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MARTIN, LISA L.), 1994-1995 (Box R3393)
- AC.2001.013: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2001; AC.2001.013; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
  - Bellagio Conference and Study Center, 120; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MASON, LUCIA), 1993-1997 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MBOW, PENDA), 1994-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MEREI, ANNA), 1995-1996 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MERZ, JOHANNES), 1995-1996 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MIMS, CEDRIC A.), 1993-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MINDLIN, BETTY), 1993-1996 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MINER, VALERIE), 1993-1998 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MITCHINSON, WENDY), 1993-1994 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MNTHALI, FELIX WINFRID JAMES), 1993-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MONTECINO, ALFONSO), 1993-1994 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MONTEMAYOR, CARLOS), 1993-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MOORE, MICHAEL STEPHEN), 1995-2000 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MORAVEC, PAUL), 1992-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MORAWSKI, STEFAN TADEUSZ), 1994-1996 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MORIMURA, SUSUMU), 1994-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MOZLEY, ROBERT F.), 1993-1998 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MUKHERJI, SHEKHAR), 1993-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MURTHY, ANANTHA) (DID NOT GO), 1994-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (MYSLIWIEC, KAROL), 1994-2000 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NAGEL, JOANE), 1994-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NAPARSTEK, ARTHUR J.), 1994-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NDLOVU, LINDELA ROWLAND) (CO-RESIDENT: SIBANDA LINDIWE MAJELE), 1994-1997 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NEALE, STEPHEN), 1994-1995 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NELSON, SARAH MILLEDGE), 1995-1997 (Box R3394)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NEWSON, DAVID DUNLOP), 1993-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NEWSON, ROBERT), 1993-1996 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NIES, JUDITH), 1996-1997 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NIU WEN-YUAN), 1995-1996 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (NJEUMA, MARTIN ZACHARY), 1996 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OBEYESEKERE, GANANATH), 1993-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OCULI, OKELLO), 1992-1994 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ODA, MAKOTO), 1992-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OGHIAKHE, SUNDAY), 1994-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OKOME, ONOOKOME), 1995-1997 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OLALQUIAGA, CELESTE), 1992-1998 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OLSEN, FRANCES), 1993-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OPPENHEIMER, AHARON), 1993-1994 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OSBORNE, BRIAN S.), 1995-1996 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OSTRO, BART DAVID), 1994-1997 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OSUNDARE NIYI) (DID NOT GO), 1994-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (OXNAM, ROBERT B.) (DID NOT GO), 1993-1996 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PALEI, MARINA), 1994-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PANJWANI MIRIAM DOSSAL), 1994-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PAPERNO, IRINA), 1995-1998 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PAPON, CHRISTIANE MARIE-LOUISE), 1993-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PARKS, SUZAN-LORI), 1993-1994 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PELLICER, OLGA), 1990-1994 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PEREZ-TAMAYO, RUY), 1994-1996 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PERIS, MERLIN), 1993-1995 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PETERSEN, KERRY A.), 1993-1994 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PHILLIPS, CARYL), 1993-1994 (Box R3395)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PONDICK, RONA), 1995-1996 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (POUDYAL, ANANTA RAJ), 1995-1997 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (POZZATTI, RUDY), 1994-1995 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PRESSBURGER, THOMAZ MIGUEL), 1994-1996 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PUPO-WALKER, ENRIQUE), 1993-1996 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (PYAKURYAL, BISHWAMBHER), 1995-1997 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (REID-GREEN, CAROLYN), 1994-2000 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (RESNIK, REGINA), 1995-1997 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (REVARD, CARTER C.), 1996-1998 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (REYES SCHRAMM, ADELAIDA), 1995-1999 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (RHODES, FRANK H. T.), 1994-1996 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (RICHTER, INGO), 1992-1995 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (RIFBJERG, KLAUS), 1992-1994 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (RIZZINI, IRENE), 1993-1994 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ROLNICK, NEIL B.), 1993-1995 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ROOT, RICHARD K.), 1994-1995 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ROSENTHAL, MIRIAM K.), 1996-1997 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ROUSSEAU, ANN MARIE), 1993-1996 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SAAR, BETYE), 1993-1995 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SAFA, HELEN M. ICKEN), 1995-1996 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SAID, EDWARD W.) (DID NOT GO), 1993-1994 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SAJJAD, KAUSAR), 1994-1996 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SAND, PETER H.), 1995-1996 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SANDY, GERALD NEIL), 1992-1997 (Box R3396)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SARASON, BARBARA RYRHOLM) (CO-RESIDENT: SARASON, IRWIN GERALD), 1994-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SAVRAN, DAVID), 1994-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SAYERS, JANET), 1995-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SCHIPPER, MINEKE), 1993-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SCHLESINGER, MARK), 1995-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SCHMIDT, GUSTAV FRIEDRICH), 1993-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SCHOFIELD, ANN), 1994-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SCHORR, DANIEL L.), 1994-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SCHORR, LISBETH BABERGER), 1994-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SCHWEITZER, GLENN E.) (CO-RESIDENT: TOTCHENYI, LEV V.), 1995-1997 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SEGAL, STANTON), 1993-1994 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SELZ, PETER), 1993-1997 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SEMPLE, MAGGIE) (DID NOT GO), 1995-1997 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SESHADRI, C.V.) (DID NOT GO), 1994-1995 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SHAPIRO, LUCY), 1995-1997 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SHAY, JONATHAN), 1995-1997 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SHENHAR-ALROY, ALIZA), 1992-1998 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SHICHOR, YITZHAK), 1995-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SHNIRELMAN, VICTOR A.), 1994-2000 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SILBEY, ROBERT J.), 1994-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SILBEY, SUSAN S.), 1994-1999 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SILVER, SHEILA), 1994-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SINGH, AMRITJIT), 1992-1997 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SINGPURWALLA, NOZER D.), 1993-1994 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SKIPITARES, THEODORA), 1995-1999 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SMITH, ALEXIS), 1994-1996 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SMITH, BARBARA HERNSTEIN), 1994-1995 (Box R3397)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SMITH, JEAN EDWARD), 1992-1999 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SOMLAI, PETER), 1995-1998 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SOUTHERN, EILEEN J.), 1995-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SPEAR, RICHARD E.), 1995-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SPITZER, LEO), 1994-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (STEWART, FRANK HENDERSON), 1995-1997 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (STOCK, BRIAN CHARLES), 1994-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (STOLL, DAVID MATTHEW), 1995-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (STRASSER, SUSAN), 1996-1999 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (STRAUSS, PETER L.), 1993-1995 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (STRONG, TRACY B.), 1994-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SUBEDI, ABHI), 1995-1998 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (SZATHMARY, EORS), 1992-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TALISAYON, SERAFIN D.), 1992-2000 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TATUM, JAMES), 1993-1995 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TAYLOR, DIANA L.), 1995-2000 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (THOMPSON, COLIN), 1992-1995 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TINKER, IRENE), 1993-1997 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TOKER, FRANKLIN K.), 1993-1994 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TOLBERT, NATHAN EDWARD), 1993-1995 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TORRISET, KJELL), 1995-1999 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TRETYAK, OLGA A.), 1994-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TV-CASPER, LINDA), 1993-1994 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TYSON, RUEL WILLOUGHBY), 1994-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (TZANAKAKIS, JOHN-MINOS E.), 1992-1994 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ULTAN, LLOYD), 1994-1996 (Box R3398)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (VALENSTEIN, ELLIOT SPIRO), 1992-1995 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (VALKI, LASZLO), 1993-1994 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (VAN ESTERIK, PENNY) (PENELOPE BRETT), 1994-1995 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (VAN HOLDE, KENSAL EDWARD), 1993-1995 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (VERCOE, JOHN EDWARD), 1993-1994 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (VIROLI, MAURIZIO) (DID NOT GO), 1993-1994 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WALKER, CHERYL), 1993-1997 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WANG, LUNING) (DID NOT GO), 1996-1997 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WARREN, ELIZABETH), 1994-2001 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WASHINGTON, A. EUGENE) (DID NOT GO), 1995-1996 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WEINGARTNER, RUDOLPH H.), 1993-1996 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WEXLER, KENNETH), 1995-1997 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WILSON, MARY ELIZABETH), 1995-1996 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WINSOR, PHILIP), 1995-1996 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WISEMAN, FREDERICK) (DID NOT GO), 1996-1997 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WONG, SHAWN S.), 1993-1996 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WOODMAN, BETTY) (ELIZABETH ABRAHAMS), 1994-1995 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (WOODWARD, PETER ROBERT), 1993-1996 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (YANG LIAN), 1994-1996 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (YOUNG, ANTHONY), 1994-1998 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ZHOU LONG), 1994-1995 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ZHUK, SERGEI IVANOVICH), 1995-2000 (Box R3399)
    - 120 - SCHOLARS (ZUCKER, BAT-AMI), 1994-1996 (Box R3399)
- AC.2001.029: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2000; AC.2001.029; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2001.029.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - AH 9441 - ARIZONA COUNCIL ON THE HUMANITIES AND PUBLIC POLICY - COMMUNITY DIALOGUE ON PUBLIC EDUCATION AND ACADEMIC FREEDOM, 1994-1998 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9452 - NATIONAL COUNCIL ON RELIGION AND PEACE (SRI LANKA) - MULTIRELIGIOUS COOPERATION FOR PEACE, 1994-1999 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9518 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - ARAB FILM SERIES PROJECT, 1994-1998 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9541 - CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - BOARD DEVELOPMENT FOR CENTER FOR LESBIAN AND GAY STUDIES (CLAGS), 1995-1998 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9542 - NEW SCHOOL FOR SOCIAL RESEARCH - CONFERENCE: "TECHNOLOGY AND THE REST OF CULTURE", 1995-1997 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9544 - TUCSON COMMUNITY FOUNDATION - COMMUNITY DIALOGUE ON THE ISSUE OF CENSORSHIP, 1993-1999 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9603 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - "CHICANA ART, A MULTIMED lA DATABASE" PROJECT, 1995-2000 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9604 - ATLATL- CONFERENCE: "NATIVE ARTS NETWORK: 96", 1995-1997 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9608 - IMAGES OF AFRICA (DENMARK) - "THE SAGA OF THE SLAVES", 1995-1997 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9609 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - REVISED HISTORY STANDARDS, 1995-1997 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9611 - CAMBODIAN NETWORK COUNCIL - RESTORING PUPPETS, 1995-1999 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9612 - CARNEGIE INSTITUTE - THREE RIVERS ARTS FESTIVAL 1996 PUBLIC ART INITIATIVE, 1995-1997 (Box R3400)
    - AH 9615 - PROJECT ROW HOUSES - ARTISTS' INSTALLATIONS IN HOUSTON, 1995-1997 (Box R3401)
    - AH 9616 - INSTITUTE FOR ADVANCED STUDY -1996-1997 SPECIAL FOCUS PROGRAM (Box R3401)
    - AH 9617 - MUSEUM OF OCEANIC AND AFRICAN ARTS (FRANCE) - SYMPOSIUM ON "POST-COLONIALISM", 1996-1997 (Box R3401)
    - AH 9622 - RECORDED ANTHOLOGY OF AMERICAN MUSIC- AFRICAN-AMERICAN FOLK MUSIC, 1995-1999 (Box R3401)
    - AH 9624 - ARTS ALIVE INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL (SOUTH AFRICA) - PARTICIPATION OF BAABA MAAL AT FESTIVAL, 1996-1997 (Box R3401)
    - AH 9625 - ASIAN AMERICAN WRITERS' WORKSHOP - ANTHOLOGY ON SUBJECT OF AMERICA, 1996-1999 (Box R3401)
    - AH 9626 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF ARTISTS' ORGANIZATIONS - MEETING OF YOUNG ARTISTS, 1996-1999 (Box R3401)
    - AH 9628 - AMERICAN ASSEMBLY - ARTS AND THE PUBLIC PURPOSE, 1996-1998 (Box R3401)
    - AH 9631 - MONTEMAYOR, CARLOS- CONTEMPORARY MAYA LITERATURE, 1992-1999 (Box R3401)
    - AH 9631 - MONTEMAYOR, CARLOS- CONTEMPORARY MAYA LITERATURE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1992-1999 (Box R3401, Box R3401A)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2001.029.2; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - AS 9213 - SOCIETY FOR PROMOTION OF WASTELANDS DEVELOPMENT - ESTABLISH ITS RESOURCE ECONOMICS UNIT, 1991-1998 (Box R3401)
    - AS 9338 - FUND FOR THE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF AGRICULTURAL ECONOMISTS - XXII CONFERENCE, 1993-1995 (Box R3401)
    - AS 9409 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE- SURVEY OF MAIZE VIRUSES IN ZIMBABWE, 1991-2000 (Box R3401)
    - AS 9411 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (ICIPE)(KENYA) - THIRD INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON TROPICAL ENTOMOLOGY, 1994-1995 (Box R3401)
    - AS 9440 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP AND BOOK ON AFRICA'S MAIZE-BASED GREEN REVOLUTION, 1994-1997 (Box R3401)
    - AS 9536 - OREGON STATE UNIVERSITY - DEVELOPMENT OF NUCELLAR CELLS FOR APOMIXIS IN RICE, 1995-1997 (Box R3401)
    - AS 9540 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH - SECOND INTERNATIONAL CROP SCIENCES CONGRESS, 1995-1998 (Box R3401)
    - AS 9541 - ASTIER, MARTA - LEGUMES TO IMPROVE VOLCANIC SOILS IN MICHOACAN, MEXICO, 1995-1998 (Box R3401)
    - AS 9548 - CENTER FOR RESEARCH AND ADVANCED STUDIES (CINVESTAV) (MEXICO) - BIOLOGICAL NITROGEN FIXATION IN LEGUMES AND MAIZE IN TROPICAL REGIONS, 1995-1998 (Box R3401)
    - AS 9601 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - SOIL COMPONENT OF COLLABORATIVE STUDY OF CASSAVA IN AFRICA, 1995-1998 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9602 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - DROUGHT TOLERANCE AND MAIZE SYMPOSIUM, 1996-1998 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9607 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (DAVIS) - EFFECT OF LOW PHYTATE MAIZE ON ABSORPTION OF IRON, 1996-1997 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9608 - MALAWI- AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - REVOLVING FUND COVERING AGRICULTURAL INPUTS MARKETING AND DISTRIBUTION, 1995-1998 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9610 - CAB INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - PLANT PATHOLOGY IN EAST AFRICA TRAINING COURSE, 1996-1999 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9611 - MWANGI, PETERSON - NATURAL RESOURCE USE IN SUSTAINABLE MAIZE PRODUCTION IN KENYA, 1996-1999 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9615 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - GLOBAL AGRICULTURAL SCIENCE POLICY CONFERENCE, 1995-1998 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9616 - NORTHWESTERN UNIVERSITY - INTEGRATED PEST MANAGEMENT IN INDONESIA, 1995-1997 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9619 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (KENYA) - FOURTH INTERNATIONAL PERIODIC EXTERNAL REVIEW, 1996-1998 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9620 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - CURRICULUM REVIEW WORKSHOP, 1996-1998 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9622- INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT (MEXICO) - FIFTH REGIONAL MAIZE CONFERENCE FOR EASTERN AND SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1996-1997 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9623 - GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY- BIOTECHNOLOGY SEMINAR, 1996-1997 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9626 - UNITED STATES - AGRICULTURE (DEPARTMENT OF) - PLANT GENOME V MEETING, 1996 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9628 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - FOOD INSECURITY IN SOUTHERN AFRICA SYMPOSIUM, 1996 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9629 - FUND FOR THE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF AGRICULTURAL ECONOMISTS - XXIII CONFERENCE, 1996-1997 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9630 - INTERNATIONAL LIVESTOCK RESEARCH INSTITUTE (ETHIOPIA) - WORKSHOP ON DAIRY POLICY RESEARCH, 1996-1998 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9632 - INTER-AMERICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK- REGIONAL FUND FOR AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGY, 1996-1998 (Box R3402)
    - AS 9634 - KEYSTONE CENTER - LONG-TERM FOOD SECURITY WORKSHOP, 1996-1998 (Box R3403)
    - AS 9636 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR INFORMATION ON COVER CROPS (HONDURAS) - COVER CROPS AND GREEN MANURES, 1996-1998 (Box R3403)
    - AS 9637 - TEXAS A, 1996-1998 (Box R3403)
    - AS 9638 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIRST ALL AFRICA CROP SCIENCE CONGRESS, 1995-1998 (Box R3403)
    - AS 9639 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - RESEARCH ASSISTANTSHIP POSITION FOR D.P. BWAMIKI (RESCINDED), 1996-1997 (Box R3403)
    - AS 9642 - NETWORK PROGRAM (MEXICO) - CONSOLIDATION OF THE RURAL INFORMATION NETWORK, 1996-1999 (Box R3403)
    - AS 9643 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - WORKSHOP ON GREEN MANURE AND COVER CROPS FOR SMALLHOLDER FARMERS, 1995-1998 (Box R3403)
    - AS 9704 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - NUTRIENT TRANSFERS AND PRODUCTIVITY AND SUSTAINABILITY OF ECOSYSTEMS, THE NUTMON PROJECT, 1994-1999 (Box R3403)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2001.029.3; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - EO 9321 - UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA RESEARCH FOUNDATION, INC. - TELEPHONE SURVEY ON URBAN INEQUALITY, 1993-1997 (Box R3403)
    - EO 9526 - YOUTHBUILD U.S.A. - AFFILIATED NETWORK SUPPORT, 1994-1998 (Box R3403)
    - EO 9602 - HOME CARE ASSOCIATES TRAINING INSTITUTE - CORE SUPPORT FOR HEALTH CARE EMPLOYMENT AND TRAINING, 1995-1997 (Box R3404)
    - EO 9611 - MIDWEST CENTER FOR LABOR RESEARCH - CORE ACTIVITIES AND EVALUATION CRITERIA TO MEASURE PROGRESS, 1993-1999 (Box R3404)
    - EO 9614 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF THE CHURCHES OF CHRIST IN THE USA - BURNED CHURCHES FUND, 1996-1998 (Box R3404)
    - EO 9616 - FAIR EMPLOYMENT COUNCIL OF GREATER WASHINGTON - CORE SUPPORT, 1996-2000 (Box R3404)
    - EO 9701 - PUBLIC/PRIVATE VENTURES - MOBILITY-TO-WORK PROJECT, 1994-1999 (Box R3405)
    - EO 9701 - PUBLIC/PRIVATE VENTURES - MOBILITY-TO-WORK PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1999 (Box R3405)
    - EO 9705 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - NATIONAL COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT POLICY ANALYSIS NETWORK, 1996-1998 (Box R3405)
    - EO 9711 - KNOWLEDGE NETWORK FOR ALL AMERICA'S CHILDREN - IMPACT ASSESSMENT OF 1976 ADVANCED LEADERSHIP TRAINING PROGRAM FOR MINORITY EDUCATORS, 1997 (Box R3405)
- AC.2001.034: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1978-2001; AC.2001.034; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2001.034.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - EO 9527 - BUSINESS FOR SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY EDUCATION FUND - URBAN UNEMPLOYMENT, 1995-1998 (Box R3406)
    - EO 9720 - CENTER FOR LAW AND SOCIAL POLICY - CONFERENCE ON JOBS AND TANF LEGISLATION, 1997-1998 (Box R3406)
    - EO 9721 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA (CHAPEL HILL) - WORKSHOP ON METROPOLITAN ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT, 1997 (Box R3406)
    - EO 9723 - CLEVELAND COMMUNITY BUILDING INITIATIVE - COMMUNITY-BUILDING CONFERENCE, 1995-1998 (Box R3406)
    - EO 9724 - CHATHAM-SAVANNAH YOUTH FUTURES AUTHORITY - COMMUNITY-BUILDING CONFERENCE, 1997-1999 (Box R3406)
    - EO 9725 - RHEEDLEN CENTERS FOR CHILDREN AND FAMILIES - COMMUNITY-BUILDING CONFERENCE, 1997 (Box R3406)
    - EO 9726 - NATIONAL ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND LAW CENTER- COMMUNITY-BUILDING CONFERENCE, 1997-1999 (Box R3406)
    - EO 9740 - UPLIFT, INC.- GREENSBORO STORY TELLING PROJECT, 1996-1999 (Box R3406)
  - Global Environment (GE), AC.2001.034.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - GE 9118 - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT- PHOTOVOLTAIC LANTERNS, 1991-1998 (Box R3406)
    - GE 9206 - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT - CANE-TO-ENERGY TEST PROGRAM IN THAILAND, 1991-1998 (Box R3406)
    - GE 9305 - UNIVERSITY OF THE WEST INDIES (JAMAICA) - PROJECT "ENERGY IN CARIBBEAN SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT", 1992-2000 (Box R3406)
    - GE 9506 - BIOMASS USERS NETWORK INC., 1989-1998 (Box R3406)
    - GE 9607 - ASIA NETWORK FOR SMALL SCALE AGRICULTURAL BIORESOURCES (NEPAL) - POTENTIAL OF PLANT OILS AS SUBSTITUTES FOR DIESEL FUEL, 1995-1998 (Box R3406)
    - GE 9608 - GREENPEACE ENVIRONMENTAL TRUST (ENGLAND) - OXFORD SOLAR INVESTMENT SUMMIT, 1996-1997 (Box R3407)
    - GE 9610 - BIOMASS USERS NETWORK (ZIMBABWE) - EFFICACY OF PLANT OILS AS A POTENTIONAL SOURCE OF ENERGY IN ZIMBABWE, 1996-1998 (Box R3407)
    - GE 9702 - BRAZILIAN ASSOCIATION FOR LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT - WORKSHOP TO PREPARE LEAD PRESENTATIONS FOR THE FIVE-YEAR FOLLOW-UP MEETING (RIO PLUS 5), 1997 (Box R3407)
  - Health Sciences (HS), AC.2001.034.3; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - HS 9430 - BEIJING CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL (CHINA) - ACUTE MOTOR AXONAL NEUROPATHY OF CHILDREN, 1993-1999 (Box R3407)